Bruno Ferreira De Santi Murino

bfsmurino@gmail.com www.brunomurino.com 6B Willesden Lane, London, NW6 7SR Visa: **Italian citizen** +44 (0) 78989 76564 github.com/brunomurino linkedin.com/in/brunomurino

I graduated in July 2017 with a First Class in my BSc in Physics from the University of São Paulo. After graduating I immediately started a master degree in theoretical physics and after 5 months I also started working at Ernst & Young to try something out of the academy that would still use my analytical and problem solving skills. After 4 months working at EY I quit to dedicate myself fully to the master degree. However, after I finished the degree's coursework (1 year) I concluded that theoretical physics research wasn't the path for me, so I started studying web development/data science and relocated to London to find my first professional role in software development/data science. I'm currently looking for a challenging junior/graduate web developer/data scientist role where I can put my analytical skills to good use and further develop my tech skills.

Education

Nov. 2018 – Dec. 2018 - Deep Learning Specialisation

(deeplearning.ai, Coursera)

Sep. 2018 - Oct. 2018 - Machine Learning with TensorFlow on Google Cloud Platform Specialisation (Google Cloud, Coursera)

July 2017 – July 2018 - MSc in Theoretical Physics; Dropped out after 1 year

(University of São Paulo, Brazil)

Relevant Coursework: Quantum Information, Quantum Mechanics, Formation and Evolution of Galaxies.

Research: Research on Category Theory/Categorial QFT funded by CNPq.

Feb. 2014 – July. 2017 - BSc in Physics; 8.1 (Equiv. UK First class honours)

(University of São Paulo, Brazil)

Relevant Coursework: Courses on Data Processing, Statistical Methods and Statistical Mechanics.

Research: Introductory research on String Theory funded by FAPESP.

MOOC's

Linkedin Learning (Lynda): Advanced SQL for Data Scientists, Apache Spark Essential Training, JavaScript Essential Training, Learning Docker.

Datacamp: Introduction to PySpark, Supervised Learning with scikit-learn, Importing Data in Python (Part 2), Data

Visualisation with Seaborn.

Alura: HTML5 & CSS3 I, HTML5 & CSS3 II, Excel I, Excel II.

Experience

Dec. 2017 - Mar. 2018 - Trainee Advisory Consultant at Ernst & Young

(São Paulo, Brazil)

I was part of the team responsible for helping external auditors deal with the vast amounts of financial data, up to 200 million transactions, by using softwares such as ACL and MS Excel. During my period there I was in charge of 2 major clients, one of them being one of the biggest aviation companies in Latin America, which at the time was ending it's fiscal year.

Aug. 2017 - Dec. 2017 - Teaching Assistant of Physics IV at University of São Paulo

(São Paulo, Brazil)

Third year course of the BSc in Physics. The course had around 80 students enrolled. I gave weekly lectures, graded problem sets, and conducted weekly recitation sessions. Topics included were Optics, Special Relativity, and Covariant Formulation of Electromagnetism.

Aug. 2017 - Dec. 2017 - Self-employed Private Math tutor

(São Paulo, Brazil)

Tutored Mathematics at the Secondary Education level. I gave weekly tutoring sessions to a 10 year old kid.

Programming Skills

Languages: Python, SQL, ACL, Matlab, HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

Languages

English (Fluent, IELTS 7.5)

Portuguese (Native)

French (Basic)

Volunteering

July 2016 - July 2017 - Volunteer Physics Teacher

(ETEC Jaraguá, Brazil)

Weekly lectures on physics were given to high school students of ETEC Jaraguá, a Technical Public School, aiming to improve results on the Public Schools BRian Olympics of Physics (OBFEP).

Awards

Aug. 2018 - International Science and Engineering Excellence Award

(Queen Mary's University of London, UK)

To reward academic achievement and help attract the brightest and best students from overseas. (Received upon application to MSc in Theoretical Physics, which was accepted but I declined the offer.)